(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-19T01:30:56.762738",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あ、おはよう！
Ah, good morning!
私は今来たところ。
I just got here myself.
全然待ってないよ。
I didn't wait at all.
むしろ、今日は来てくれてありがとう。
Actually, thank you for coming today.
いい天気だね。
It's beautiful weather, isn't it?
私さ、
You know...
ずっと君とこうやって、
I've always wanted to do this with you,
公園とかお散歩したいと思ってたんだ。
just taking a stroll in the park like this.
あのさ、
Hey...
手、繋いでもいいかな？
would it be okay if we held hands?
やった！繋いじゃおう！
Yay! Let's hold hands!
手を繋いでると、
Holding hands like this...
なんかドキドキするね。
...makes my heart beat a little faster.
いよいよこれから生誕ライブか。
Our birthday live is finally about to start.
緊張するなー。
I'm so nervous.
君も、もちろん来てくれるよね？
You're coming too, right?
ありがとう。
Thank you.
今日のために、
For today,
歌とかダンスとかいっぱい練習してきたから、
I've practiced singing and dancing so much,
絶対見てほしいと思ってたんだ。
so I really wanted you to see it.
絶対見つけるね！
I'll definitely find you in the crowd!
あ、あそこにベンチがあるよ。
Oh, look, there's a bench over there.
ちょっと座って話そう。
Let's sit down and chat for a bit.
なんかさ、
You know,
一つの椅子に隣同士で座るとさ、
sitting right next to each other on one bench...
なんか、ドキドキするね。
...makes me feel kind of nervous.
かわいい。
You're so cute.
ところで、お昼ご飯食べた？
By the way, have you had lunch yet?
そっか、まだ食べてないんだ。
I see, so you haven't eaten yet.
そうだと思って。
...so I thought.
実は今日、君のために...
Actually, today, just for you...
手作りのお弁当作ってきたんだ。
I made a homemade bento!
一緒に食べよう？
Let's eat together, okay?
ありがとう。
Thank you.
じゃっじゃーん！
Tada!
見て。
Look at this.
これお弁当箱可愛いでしょ？
Isn't this bento box cute?
中身何入ってると思う？
What do you think is inside?
卵焼き？
Rolled omelet?
唐揚げ？
Fried chicken?
ハンバーグ？
Salisbury steak?
うーん、なるほど。
Hmm, I see.
正解は...
The correct answer...
こちらでしたー！
...is right here!
わあ！美味しそう！
Wow! It looks delicious!
どうかな？AZKiの手作りお弁当。
What do you think of AZKi's homemade bento?
題して...
I call it...
「あなたのハートをゼロゲッサーお弁当」
"The Guess-Your-Heart-to-Zero Bento!"
だよ。
"The Guess-Your-Heart-to-Zero Bento!"...
君の好きな卵焼きもちゃんと入ってます。
Your favorite rolled omelet is in here too.
正解だよ。
You got it right!
それじゃあ、何から食べる？
Well then, what should we eat first?
ソーセージ？
The sausage?
トマト？
The tomato?
卵焼き？
The rolled omelet?
やっぱり大好物の卵焼きからか。
Mmhmm, starting with your absolute favorite, I see.
本当好きだよね。
You really love them, don't you?
じゃあさ、
In that case...
あーんしてあげよっか。
...should I feed you?
もう、頷きすぎだよ。
Gosh, you're nodding so hard!
可愛いな。
So cute.
はい、じゃあ、あーん。
Here, open wide... "Ahhh."
どう？美味しい？
How is it? Delicious?
ありがとう。嬉しい。
Thank you! I'm so glad.
はい、じゃあもう一口。あーん。
Here, one more bite... "Ahhh."
美しそうに食べるね。
You look so happy eating it!
作った甲斐があった。
Making it was totally worth it.
美しそうに食べてる君も、AZKiは好きだよ。
I love seeing you enjoy your food like this.
食べてる君の姿見てたら、AZKiも元気出た。
Watching you eat has energized me too!
今日の生誕ライブも頑張れそうだよ。
I feel like I can give it my all at today's concert.
それじゃあ、そろそろリハーサルの時間だから、
Well, it's about time for rehearsal,
行ってくるね。
so I've got to head out.
絶対見つけるからね。
I'll make sure to find you in the crowd!
ライブが終わったら、また待ち合わせね。
Let's meet up here again after the show, okay?
せーの！
One, two!
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's not good enough
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
See, that's not going to do
心は進化するよ
My heart is going to keep evolving
もっと もっと
More and more
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If our relationship will fade away once put into words
言葉を消せばいいやって
Then we should just do away with words
思ってた 恐れてた
That's what I thought, and what I feared
だけど あれ？ なんかちがうかも...
But wait, maybe that's not quite right...
せんりのみちもいっぽから！
A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step!
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
With a resolve as solid as a stone
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ？
Even dust piles up to become a proper lady?
「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で！
Skipping the "S," wait, I mean with all my might!
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Soft and fluffy, floating around
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
When you call out my name
それだけで
Just that alone
宙へ浮かぶ
Makes me float to the heavens
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Floating around, soft and fluffy
あなたが笑っている
When you are smiling
それだけで
Just that alone
笑顔になる
Brings a smile to my face
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, dear God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it was just a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが
That we were able to meet
しあわせなの
Makes me so incredibly happy
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's not good enough
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
See, that's not going to do
心は進化するよ
My heart is going to keep evolving
もっと もっと
More and more
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
That's right, I don't want it to end like that
ねえ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, we're not quite there yet
私のこと見ててね
Keep your eyes on me
ずっと ずっと
Forever and ever
私の中のあなたほど あなたの中の私の存在は
My presence inside of you isn't nearly as big as your presence is inside of me yet
まだまだ大きくないことも
My presence inside of you isn't nearly as big as your presence is inside of me yet...
わかってるけれど
I know that, but still...
今この同じ瞬間
At this very moment
共有してる実感
Feeling this shared connection
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ！
Even dust piles up to become a proper lady!
略して？ちりつもやまとなでこ！
In short? The ever-accumulating lady-to-be!
くらくらり くらくらる
Dizzy and spinning, round and round
あなたを見上げたら
When I look up at you
それだけで
Just that alone
まぶしすぎて
Is so incredibly dazzling
くらくらる くらくらり
Spinning and dizzy, round and round
あなたを想っている
I am thinking of you
それだけでとけてしまう
Just that alone makes me melt
神様 ありがとう
Thank God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが
The fact that we met
しあわせなの
makes me happy
コイスル キセツハ ヨクバリ circulation
Love's season is a greedy circulation
コイスル キモチハ ヨクバリ circulation
Loving feelings are a greedy circulation
コイスル ヒトミハ ヨクバリ circulation
Loving eyes are a greedy circulation
コイスル オトメハ ヨクバリ circulation
A maiden in love is a greedy circulation
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Softly floating, softly floating
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
You call my name
それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
Just that alone makes me float into the air
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Softly floating, softly floating
あなたが笑っている
You are smiling
それだけで 笑顔になる
Just that alone brings a smile to my face
神様 ありがとう
Thank God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが
The fact that we met
しあわせなの
makes me happy
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's no good
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
Look, that's already no good
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart will evolve, more and more
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yes, I don't want it like that
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, not like that yet
私のこと 見ててね ずっとずっと
Please keep watching me, always and forever
ひとくち、ちょうだい？
A Bite, Please?
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
恋人みたいなことしてみたいの
I want to do things like lovers do
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...is what I couldn't say on our date today
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
I only want to eat one bite
目が合うだけで頬が緩む
Just our eyes meeting makes me smile
目尻のしわくちゃ たまらないの
The wrinkles at the corners of your eyes, I can't resist them
週末 弾けた恋模様
A love story that burst open over the weekend
心が微熱どころではない
My heart is far beyond a slight fever
ときめきの夢に酔いしれて
Intoxicated by this heart-throbbing dream
いっそこのまま死んでもいい…？！
I wouldn't even mind dying right now...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, it's because I love you
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
If only time would just stop
幸せを噛み締めていたいな
I want to savor this happiness
ずっとこのまま覚めないで
Please don't ever wake me up like this
あともう一口だけ
Just one more bite
許されるならば夢を見せて
If permitted, show me a dream
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
間接キスなんてもう気にしないよ
I don't even care about indirect kissing anymore
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
……あなたが好きすぎて言い出せないよ
...I love you too much to say it
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
I only want to eat one bite
もうそろそろ気持ちが爆発しそうだよ
My feelings are about to explode soon
抱きしめてみたいよ
I want to try hugging you
……でも引かれたら立ち直れないし。。
...but if you're put off, I won't recover..
臆病なの、変わらないや
I'm a coward, that hasn't changed
目が合うだけで心臓が飛ぶ
Just our eyes meeting makes my heart leap
せめて手だけは繋ぎたいの
At least I want to hold hands
週末 弾けた恋模様
A love story that burst open over the weekend
心が微熱どころではない
My heart is far beyond a slight fever
もう一度 夢に酔いしれて
Once again intoxicated by the dream
連れ出して！
Take me away!
いっそこのまま死んでもいい…？！
I wouldn't even mind dying right now...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, it's because I love you
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
If only time would just stop
幸せを噛み締めていたいな
I want to savor this happiness
ずっとこのまま覚めないで
Please don't ever wake me up like this
あともう一口だけ
Just one more bite
許されるならば夢を見せて
If permitted, show me a dream
日が暮れるまで傍に居て
Stay by my side until the sun sets
初キスはもう少し後で
The first kiss can wait a bit longer
束縛は強めでOK？
Is it okay if I'm a bit possessive?
受け止めて 受け止めて
Accept me, accept me
何も言わずに手を引いて
Take my hand without saying a word
そのまま遠くへ連れてって
And take me far away just like that
どこまでも どこまでも
Anywhere, anywhere
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...is what I couldn't say on our date today
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
I just want to have one bite...
今、私は恋してるの！
Right now, I'm in love!
はい！ということで、みんな！
Yes! So, everyone...
こんこんこんこんこんあずきー！
Kon-kon-kon-kon-kon-AZKi!
右手にマイク、左手に地図、あなたのハートを...
A microphone in my right hand, a map in my left, and your heart...
ゼロゲッサー！あずきです！
Zero-Guesser! I'm AZKi!
ということで、えー、本日は
And with that, well, today...
本日は、AZKi 7th Birthday Live 「Sweet Pop Story」にお越しくださり
Thank you so much for coming to
ありがとうございます！
AZKi's 7th Birthday Live, 'Sweet Pop Story'!
わーい、わーい、わーい！始まった、始まった！
Yay, yay, yay! It's started, it's started!
えー、なんと活動始めて7回目の誕生日を迎えることができました！
I can't believe I'm celebrating my 7th birthday since starting my activities!
本当に、本当に、いつも応援してくれる開拓者のみんなのおかげで
It's seriously all thanks to all the Pioneers who always support me...
今日の日が、この日があると思っています。いつもありがとう！
...that we can have this wonderful day. Thank you as always!
ということで、なんとね、もう今日は冒頭から、じゃじゃーん！
And with that, right from the very beginning today... Ta-da!
新衣装お披露目でございます！どうかな？どうかな？どうかな？
It's my new outfit reveal! How is it? How is it?
どう？どう？どう？どう？どう？
Do you like it? How does it look?
はい、今回の新衣装のテーマはですね、
Yes! The theme of this new outfit is...
ゆるふわ私服衣装となっております！
...a soft and fluffy casual look!
可愛いでしょ？可愛いでしょ？はい！
Cute, right? Isn't it cute? Yes!
ということでね、こういう私服っぽくて可愛い衣装がいいな、欲しいなって思っていたので
I've always wanted a cute, everyday casual outfit like this...
今回、お仕立てしていただきました！
...so I had it custom-made this time!
そしてね、今日のこのライブステージもこの衣装に合せて
And today's live stage has also been styled...
なんと、なんと、見てください！みなさん
...to match this outfit! Look at this, everyone!
ちょっとお部屋っぽく、ちょっとデートモードに行けそうな
It's styled like a cozy room, where we can get into...
ステージになっております！
...a lovely date mode!
この新衣装にぴったりのステージになってます！
It's the perfect stage for my new outfit!
はい！
Yes!
ということで、今日はですね、この配信のハッシュタグ！
So, today, the hashtag for this stream is...
右上、こっち！これこれこれこれこれこれ！
...right up here on the top-right! This one!
「#AZKi生誕ライブ2025」で
'#AZKi生誕ライブ2025'!
たくさんたくさんポストしてください！
Please post tons and tons of tweets!
スクショとか感想とか全部全部AZKiもチェックしますんで
I'll be checking your screenshots and thoughts,
可愛いAZKiをスクショするんだ！
so make sure to screenshot the cute AZKi!
よろしくね！
Alright?
お願いします！
Please do!
そしてそし、今日はですね、新衣装のお披露目だけでなく
And also, today, we don't just have the outfit reveal...
重大発表もありますので
...we also have a major announcement!
ぜひ最後まで見てください！よろしくね
So please watch until the very end! I count on you!
はい、ということでね、さっそくライブが始まったわけなんですが
So, we started the live right away...
ちょっと今回は「Sweet Pop Story」ということで
...but since the theme this time is 'Sweet Pop Story'...
物語風に、ちょっとデートなんかしてみちゃったり
...we wanted to give it a storybook feel, like going on a date.
はいそして今日のライブ楽しんでいただけたらなと思います
Yes (laughs). I hope you enjoy today's live concert.
で、1曲目は「恋愛サーキュレーション」、そして2曲目は「ヒトクチ、チョウダイ？」っていうね
Our first song was 'Renai Circulation', and the second was 'Hitokuchi, Choudai?'...
オリジナル曲でございました！
...which is my original song!
どうだったかな？どうだった？可愛かった？
How was it? Did you like it? Was it cute?
ということで、ここから、なんとみんなお待ちかねの
And now, we are moving on to the highly anticipated...
ゲストブロックになります！
...guest block!
大好きなあのメンバーと、可愛い曲を
I'll be singing a super cute song with that member...
歌っちゃいますので、ぜひぜひ楽しんでいただけたらと思います！
...who I absolutely love, so I hope you enjoy it!
それでは行くよ！
Alright, here we go!
どうぞ！
Please enjoy!
浮つく甘い街の喧騒
The restless hustle and bustle of the sweet town
故に感情線は渋滞
Because of that, my emotional lines are jammed
「僕に関係ない」とか言って
Saying 'It has nothing to do with me'
心模様 白く染まって
While my heart's landscape is dyed in pure white
だけどどうやったって釣り合わない
But no matter what, we just don't match
いたずらに笑う横顔に乾杯
A toast to your profile as you laugh mischievously
酸いも甘いもわからないの
I don't even know the bitters or sweets of it
きっと君の前では迷子
I'm surely lost whenever I'm in front of you
溶かしてはランデブー
Melting away on this rendezvous
プラトニックになってく
We're slowly becoming platonic
ほろ苦い期待 張り裂けてしまいそう
My bittersweet expectations feel like they're about to burst
だから
So...
夢惑う
Dreaming and wandering...
想いならば
If they are feelings,
聞かせて
let me hear them.
その声を
Let me hear your voice.
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I were to be dyed in your color, completely dyed...
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
I'd let my heart wander, so don't look away.
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking of you, keep thinking of you.
桃色の心予報
A peach-colored heart forecast.
今混ざってしまえば 混ざってしまえば
If we were to blend together now, completely blend...
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって保存
Overlapping with you, our gazes meeting as love intertwines.
ロマンスは止まらない
This romance won't stop.
失敗したらグッバイスステップ保存
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神様どうか 今日は味方して
Oh God, please side with me today.
おかしな君は笑って
You laugh in your strange way,
逆さま世界が顔出して
as an upside-down world shows its face.
夢ならまだ覚めないで
If this is a dream, please don't wake me yet.
心模様 赤に染まってく
My heart's pattern is turning red.
冷静沈着では どう頑張ったって無い
Being calm and collected? No matter how I try, it's impossible.
大体 視界に居ない ちょっとlateなスターリナイト
For the most part, you're not in sight on this slightly late starry night.
最悪な昨日にさえ さよなら言いたいよな
I want to say goodbye even to the worst yesterday.
甘いおまじないかけられてしまいそう
It feels like a sweet spell is about to be cast on me.
だから
That's why...
この夜を越えてゆけ
...we must cross over this night.
響かせて
Let it resonate.
その想いを
Let those feelings resonate.
君に染まってしまえば Ah
If I were to be dyed in your color... Ah...
君だけ想っていたいな Ah
I want to keep thinking only of you... Ah...
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I were to be dyed in your color, completely dyed...
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで保存
I'd let my heart wander, so don't look away.
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking of you, keep thinking of you.
桃色の心予報
A peach-colored heart forecast.
今伝えてしまえ 伝えてしまえば
If I were to convey it now, completely convey it...
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって Oh
Overlapping with you, our gazes meeting as love intertwines... Oh...
失敗したらグッバイスステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神様どうか 今日は味方して
Oh God, please side with me today.
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love! You absolutely must fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
It's a magic spell, decorating you and everything.
ハツコイ♡パティシエール
[Title: First Love Patissiere]
朝からビターなキモち だって知らない表情(かお)で笑った
A bitter feeling since morning, because you smiled with a face I've never seen.
ちょっと髪に触れたりしちゃって なんでハナの下伸ばしてんの！？
Even lightly touching your hair, why are you grinning like that?!
どんどん膨らんでいくジェラシー スフレみたいに甘くないよ
This jealousy keeps swelling up, it's not sweet like a soufflé.
胸いっぱいに溢れちゃって ダメダメ！気づかれちゃうよ！
It's overflowing in my chest, no, no! You're going to notice!
バレないように…でも気づいて！フクザツな乙女心
Don't let it show... but please notice! A girl's complex heart.
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love! You absolutely must fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
It's a magic spell, decorating you and everything.
恋心ちょっとキャラメリゼ
Caramelizing my love just a little bit,
焦がしたらきっと スキにさせるから！
if I burn it, I'll definitely make you fall in love with me!
今日は朝からちょっとラッキー あくびこらえた変顔見ちゃった
Today started off slightly lucky, I saw you pull a funny face trying to hold in a yawn.
肩叩きながらおはようなんて言えたらもっと…あぁ！もう！イケナイ！
If only I could pat your shoulder and say good morning... Ah! Geez! I can't!
ふぅ…ちょっと落ち着いて？モンテしすぎて零れちゃうよ
Whew... calm down a bit, okay? If you whip it too much, it'll spill over.
「なににしてんの？」ってほっぺツンツン いきなりまさかの不意打ち禁止～！
Poking my cheek while asking, "What are you doing?" No sudden surprise attacks allowed~!
メレンゲハート 耳までキュイール アツいのは私だけ？
A meringue heart, baking all the way to my ears, am I the only one who's hot?
スキすぎる！あぁ…スキすぎる！保存
I love you too much! Ah... I love you too much!
ココロからスペシャリテのアイラヴュー
From the bottom of my heart, a specialty I love you.
恋心もっとタブラージュ
Tablage my love even more,
溶けたならハート型にグラッセしよ
and once it melts, let's glaze it into a heart shape.
アナタにだけ 教えてあげる
I'll tell only you...
このキモチのヒミツ
...the secret behind these feelings.
「ダイスキだよ！」
"I love you so much!"
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love! You absolutely must fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
It's a magic spell, decorating you and everything.
あなたことデコレーション
decorating with you.
このキモチ ずっとアラカルト
This feeling is always a la carte.
おすそわけ ココロごとデコレーション
Sharing it, decorating with my whole heart.
恋心いっぱいプレゼント
A present full of love.
届いたら 私ごと召し上がれ
Once it reaches you, please eat me too.
Lalala...
なーにしよっか練習中
Practicing what we should do.
しれっとこそっと準備進行
Quietly and stealthily preparing.
心境 緊張で焦る
My state of mind, panicking with nerves.
言わんけどつよつよアリでしょ？
I won't say it, but being super strong is fine, right?
元気配るから待っちょって
Wait for me, I'll share my energy.
そうやって成長する子です
That's how this kid grows.
いいかな
Is it okay?
ゆるポンでOK？
Is loosely okay?
いちにーさん
One, two, three!
手パっちゃってOK？
Is panicking okay?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started.
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
I want you to praise me, I want you to praise me.
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll work 20% harder.
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me, I want you to watch me.
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type who grows by being showered with praise.
もう
Geez!
なぁーんにも出てこない
Nothing is coming to mind.
頭ん中真っ白だ
My head is a total blank.
さっぱりだ うんうんうん あれ？
No clue at all, yeah, yeah, yeah, huh?
まっいっか
Oh well.
凸凹な情緒 提供中
Providing uneven emotions.
ぽかんとして何しちょんの
What are you doing looking so blankly?
こんなんが通常のわたし
This is my normal self.
いいでしょ？
Sounds good, right?
それではOK？
Are you ready then?
いちにーさん
One, two, three!
落ち着きOK？
Feeling calm?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started.
どうしたらいいの？ どうしたらいいの？
What should we do? What should we do?
どうすればみんなハッピーで笑顔バッチリ
How can we make everyone happy and smiling perfectly?
こちらへどうぞ こちらへどうぞ
Come this way, come this way.
押さず慌てず並んで合図です
Line up without pushing or rushing, that's the signal.
もう
Geez!
聞こえてる？
Can you hear me?
みゃーみゃーみゃー
Meow, meow, meow.
楽しんでる？
Are you having fun?
ぽんぽんぽん
Pon, pon, pon.
こっちだよ
Over here!
少し眠いな 少し眠いな
I'm a little sleepy, I'm a little sleepy.
また明日食べて寝て今は成長期
I'll eat and sleep again tomorrow, right now I'm growing.
夢を見たいな 夢を見たいな
I want to dream, I want to dream.
どうぞくれぐれもあの、今後も
Please, by all means, you know, in the future too.
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
I want you to praise me, I want you to praise me.
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll work 20% harder.
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me, I want you to watch me.
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type who grows by being showered with praise.
またね
See you!
sweet night, sweet time
せっと陽の沈む茜の空
Setting sun in the madder red sky.
やっと目覚めたきみに挨拶
Greeting you who has finally woken up.
えっと明日は休みだから
Um, since tomorrow is a day off...
一晩中 きみといっしょに
All night long, with you.
sweet night, sweet time
眠くないよ 眠くないの
I'm not sleepy, I'm not sleepy!
sweet night, sweet time...
まだまだ遊びたい
I still want to play!
sweet night, sweet time...
話したいよ 話し足りないの
I want to talk, I haven't talked enough!
夢の中じゃ 物足りないから
Because in dreams, it's just not enough,
今夜は...
tonight...
眠らない 眠らない きみとリズム合わせ
We won't sleep, we won't sleep, matching rhythms with you,
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
enjoying turning day into night!
今だけで 眠らない 眠らない 星空さんぽして
Just for now, we won't sleep, we won't sleep, walking under the starry sky,
夜がどうか 明けないように
praying that the night won't end,
いつまでも
forever and ever...
sweet night, sweet time...
いつまでも
forever and ever...
sweet night, sweet time...
きっと話すのも笑うのも
Surely, both talking and laughing,
もっと誰かと繋がるために
are for connecting deeper with someone.
ちょっと俯いたきみへ向けて
Aimed towards you, who are looking down a little,
一晩中 歌ってもいい
I don't mind singing all night long.
sweet night, sweet time...
眠らないよ 眠らないの
I won't sleep, I won't sleep!
sweet night, sweet time...
夜ごと遊びたい
I want to play through the night!
sweet night, sweet time...
喋りたいよ 喋り足りないの
I want to chat, I haven't chatted enough!
sweet night, sweet time...
きみと朝まで
With you, until morning...
月も知らない
Not even the moon knows
ナイショ話を
about our secret talk.
パジャマのままで
Still in our pajamas,
お願い
please...
夢の中じゃ 物足りないから
Because in dreams, it's just not enough,
もう少し...
just a little more...
眠らない 眠らない きみとリズム合わせ
We won't sleep, we won't sleep, matching rhythms with you,
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
enjoying turning day into night!
今だけで 眠らない 眠らない 白む空見送って
Just for now, we won't sleep, we won't sleep, watching the dawning sky,
夜を越えよう また明日もここで会おう
let's cross the night, and meet here again tomorrow!
good night, good time...
また明日
See you tomorrow.
good night, good time...,s:
good night, good time...
また明日
See you tomorrow.
good night, good time...
というわけで、ゲストブロックをお送りしましたー！
So with that, we've finished the guest block!
どうだったかな？どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
はい、ということでゲストパートなんですが、ここまでの振り返ると
Yes, so that was the guest part, and looking back so far,
えー、いろはちゃんと「心よほう」お届けしました。
we performed "Kokoro Yohou" with Iroha-chan!
なんとね、いろはちゃんの新衣装、3Dでね、一緒にこれは「あずいろてぇてぇ」
Iroha-chan was in her new outfit, in 3D, and this was an "Azuiro teete'e" moment!
あずいろてぇてぇをしたいと思って、
I really wanted us to have an "Azuiro teete'e" (wholesome AZKi & Iroha) moment,
一緒に「歌ってみた」を出した「心よほう」を、ちょっと踊って、
so we danced to "Kokoro Yohou," which we released a cover of together,
一緒に、この新衣装であずいろてぇてぇしました。
and did some "Azuiro teete'e" together in this new outfit.
どうだった？どうだった？良かったでしょう？
How was it? How was it? It was great, right?
え、そして、えー、次は、ラミィちゃんと「初恋パティシエール」という、
And then, next, with Lamy-chan, we sang "Hatsukoi Patissiere",
ラミィちゃんのオリ曲をね、もうこの、このライブのテーマに絶対合うと思って、一緒に歌わせていただきました！
which is Lamy-chan's original song! I thought it would perfectly fit the theme of this live show, so we sang it together!
可愛かったー！
It was so cute!
え、そしてそして、えー、団長と「ホメノビ」！
And then, and then, with Danchou, we sang "Homenobi"!
これはね、ずっとずっと、あずき、一緒に団長とホメノビを歌うのが夢だったんで、
You see, for the longest time, it has been my dream to sing "Homenobi" with Danchou,
もうこのライブで実現するぞと思って、えー、ホメノビで、成長していきたいと（笑）思います！
so I wanted to make it a reality in this live show! I want to keep growing through "Homenobi"!
え、そしてそして、えー、わためと一緒に、わためのオリジナル曲、
「sweet night, sweet time...」を歌わせていただきましたー！
And then, and then, with Watame, we performed Watame's original song, "sweet night, sweet time..."!
もうこれもね、今回のコンセプトにめちゃくちゃ合う、わためとこの曲一緒に歌いたいなと思って、選曲しましたー！どうだったかなー？
I felt this one also perfectly matches our theme, and I really wanted to sing this song with Watame, so I chose it! How was it?
いやー、嬉しいね！ホロメンのオリ曲歌ったりできるの、本当にライブならではっていう感じで、えー、お送りしましたが、
Man, I'm so happy! Being able to sing Holo-members' original songs really feels like a special live experience, but...
まだまだ、ゲストパート続きますんで、えー、セトリと、あ、ゲストさんにもご注目ください！
the guest part is still continuing, so please look forward to the setlist and, ah, our guests as well!
ということで、まだまだゲストパート、いくぞー！
So, there is more of the guest part to come, let's go!
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wagging my tail, I'm scouting
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering even more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather together, we're the strongest!
「かわいにちぇっく！」
[Song: Kawaii ni Check!]
文化祭が始まる
The school festival is starting
最大規模でいきたいの
I want to do it on the grandest scale
君も参加してよね
You should participate too, okay?
ネットチケット無制限
Unlimited online tickets
校長先生もビックリ
Even the principal will be surprised
キャスト足りない 大焦り
Not enough cast members, in a huge panic
ワンワン泣いちゃう うぅ うぅ
I'm gonna cry like a dog, boo-hoo
本番間近 胃はキリキリ
The show is coming up, my stomach is in knots
運営の予算はギリギリ
The management's budget is super tight
すねちゃうぞ 泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna pout, I'm gonna cry
テレフォンナンバー pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number pi-pi-pi-pi-pi
「イケてる子を用意して」
“Get me a cool girl”
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello, I'm the organizer
可愛い子 チェックスカウター！
Checking cute girls with my scouter!
チョチョチョ チョー調子！ 美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
In-in-in-in incredibly great shape! Pretty girl captured! ☆
美少女捕まえた
I caught a beautiful girl
もしも私が死んだなら
If I ever die,
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
make it a flashy virtual funeral!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how seriously I want to do this
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wagging my tail, I'm scouting
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering even more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather together, we're the strongest!
あー無駄足三昧 しんどいわ
Ah, running around in vain is so tiring
どうしようもない無気力感
A helpless feeling of lethargy
タイムリミットは後ろちょっと！？
The time limit is close behind us!?
ここらでもういっちょ！
Let's go one more time here!
美味しいころね食べたら
If I eat a delicious Korone,
犬に金棒最強よ
an iron club for a dog, it's the strongest
東西南北駆け回り
Running all around, north, south, east, and west
まだ見ぬあの子探し出せ！
Go find that girl we haven't seen yet!
ワンワン泣いちゃう わおん
I'm gonna cry like a dog, woof!
呼んだらどこでも駆けつけます！
If you call, I'll run to you anywhere!
いい子がいたら教えてね
If there's a good girl, let me know, okay?
噛んじゃうぞ 甘えちゃうぞ
I'll bite you, I'll pamper you
テレフォンナンバー pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number pi-pi-pi-pi-pi
「イケてる子が見つかった？」
“Did you find a cool girl?”
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello, I'm the organizer
可愛い子 チェックスカウター！
Checking cute girls with my scouter!
チョチョチョ チョー調子！ 美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
In-in-in-in incredibly great shape! Pretty girl captured! ☆
美少女捕まえた
I caught a beautiful girl
もしも私が死んだなら
If I ever die,
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
make it a flashy virtual funeral!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how seriously I want to do this
尻尾振ってスカウト
Wagging my tail, I'm scouting
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering even more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather together, we're the strongest!
自選他薦は問いません
Self-recommendations or nominations are welcome
「私、君を待ってるよ」
“I'm waiting for you”
ぬふっ♪
Nufu ♪
うー あー もう はい！
Ooh, aah, enough, yes!
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No, no, I can't afford to mess up, right?
「ベイビーダンス」
[Song: Baby Dance]
真っ赤なハート差し出して... そんなのやっぱ妄想じゃん
Handing over a bright red heart... that's just a delusion after all.
そっちはどう思ってるの 言いかけてしまう無理みたい
What do you think about it? I'm about to say it, but it seems impossible.
こんなんじゃ...ってわかってるんだ 思うほどにハマっていくんだ
“Not like this...” I know that, but the more I think, the more I fall for you.
頑張りたい あたしに期待 ぎゅーだってしたいかも... かもん
I want to try hard, expect a lot from me, I might even want a hug... Come on!
ちょっとは変われていますか？ 足りないことばっかだけど
Have I changed even just a little? Even though I'm full of flaws.
ポンでコツでドジじゃない あたしだったら 君はだめだよね？
If I wasn't clumsy, awkward, and a klutz... you wouldn't like me, right?
ねえもう やだやだ ミスってらんない
Hey, no, no, I can't afford to mess up.
もう やだやだ 踊ってベイビーダンス
No, no, dance the Baby Dance.
あたしはまだ諦めない でも でも 全然だめかも
I'm still not giving up, but, but it might be completely useless.
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないの
Because, Baby Dance, I can't do it well.
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
Because, Baby Dance, I can't convey it.
もっと可愛くなりたいのに どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
Even though I want to become cuter, I don't know what to do.
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No, no, I can't afford to mess up, right?
あーやっちまった こんなはずじゃ
Ah, I messed up, it shouldn't have been like this.
どうしてどうして わかっているのに
Why, why, even though I know.
見せたくないトコ 透けちゃって 無理無理
The parts I don't want to show are showing through, impossible, impossible.
でも 期待はしたいな いいですか？
But I still want to hope, is that okay?
ポンもコツもドジも全部 あたしなんだよ ちゃんと見ていてほしい
Being clumsy, awkward, and a klutz, it's all me, I want you to look at me properly.
ねえもう やだやだ ぐずって後悔
Hey, no, no, complaining and regretting.
もう やだやだ 回ってベイビーダンス
No, no, spin, Baby Dance.
だめなあたし塗り替えたい でも でも 全然だめかも
I want to repaint my flawed self, but, but it might be completely useless.
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないの
Because, Baby Dance, I can't do it well.
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
Because, Baby Dance, I can't convey it.
もっと可愛くなりたいのに どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
Even though I want to become cuter, I don't know what to do.
まだまだ いけるかな
Can I still keep going?
な...
Now...
まだまだ言えるかな
I wonder if I can still say it...
まだまだできるかな
I wonder if I can still do it...
まだまだ うう...
Still, still... ooh...
ポンでコツでドジでダメで足りないとこばっかだって
Even if I'm clumsy, awkward, scatterbrained, and full of flaws
きっとやめないんだ
I'm sure I won't stop
ポンでコツでドジでダメで足りないとこばっかだって
Even if I'm clumsy, awkward, scatterbrained, and full of flaws
見ていてほしい ういえい！
I want you to watch me, oh yeah!
ねえもうやだやだ ミスってらんない
Hey, I hate this, I can't keep messing up
もうやだやだ 踊ってベイビーダンス
No more, just dance the Baby Dance
あたしはまだ諦めない
I'm still not giving up
ほらほらほら 全然だめじゃない
Look, look, it's not hopeless at all
だってベイビーダンス うまくできるから
Because, Baby Dance, we can do it well
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられるから
Because, Baby Dance, I can get it across
もっと可愛くなりたいから どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
Because I want to be cuter, I can work hard anytime
だってベイビーダンス きみに届くまで
Because, Baby Dance, until it reaches you
だってベイビーダンス きみに会えるまで
Because, Baby Dance, until I can meet you
もっと可愛くなりたいから どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
Because I want to be cuter, I can work hard anytime
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No way, I can't keep messing up, right?
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Service
We are スティーレ！
We are Stile!
さあ扉を開けて
Now, open the door
未知なるパラダイス 体験しよう
And experience an unknown paradise
おいで おいで YOU
Come on, come on, YOU
そうキミを待つのは 不思議なオアシス
Yes, waiting for you is a mysterious oasis
ほっこり日常に
In your warm daily life
ちょっぴりSpice
Just a little spice
くるんくるん かきまぜちゃうんだ
Spinning and spinning, let's mix it all up
くるんくるん 当店自慢のフレーバー
Spinning and spinning, our cafe's specialty flavor
サービス サービス ご褒美タイム
Service, service, reward time
おもてなし
Hospitality
ココロ込めて Welcome to...
With all our heart, welcome to...
わたし達と一緒に
Together with us
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
An dazzling wonder day-dream
愛情マシマシ 煩悩ナデナデ
Petting your worldly desires with extra affection
誠心誠意 つとめます
We will serve you with utmost sincerity
イエス！キミの元気チャージに
Yes! To recharge your energy
ひと役買えるかな
I wonder if we can do our part
こーいった感じも
This kind of style
あーいった感じも
And that kind of style too
意外と悪くないでしょ？
Isn't it surprisingly not bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, buono, I want to blend
キミにきゅんきゅんきゅん ハートにぱんぱんぱん
Heart-throbbing for you, pounding in your heart
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, buono, I want to blend
お口に合いますか？
Does it suit your taste?
お口に合うといいな
I hope you like it
ぼなぺてぃーと
Bon appétit
千客万来！
Never-ending customers!
ちょっと、なんか本意ながらも
Well, even if it's somewhat reluctant
いつだって需要は斜め上
The demand is always offbeat
そんじゃいっか ホントのわたしは
Well, that's fine, the real me is...
シークレットモードで営業スイッチオン！
Operating switch on in secret mode!
くるんくるん
Spinning and spinning
かきまぜて もっと
Mix it up even more
くるんくるん キミ仕様のフレーバー
Spinning and spinning, a flavor tailored just for you
サービス サービス 極上タイム
Service, service, premium time
癒しとは
This is what healing
かくあるべき Welcome to...
Should be like, welcome to...
わたし達のお店に
To our cafe
本日もようこそ
Welcome again today
おかえり待ってた
Welcome back, we've been waiting
リピートうれしいな
I'm so glad you're a repeat customer
店員一同 歓迎！
All staff welcome you!
イエス！キミのお疲れさまに
Yes! For your hard work
ピッタリのレシピで
With the perfect recipe
こーいうのどうかな
How about something like this?
あーいうのアリかな
Or maybe something like that?
よろこんでもらえてるかな
I wonder if you're enjoying it
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
More
Strange
Serious
Selfish
Secret
Super!
We are スティーレ！
We are Stile!
さあ扉を開けて
Now, open the door
愉快なパラダイス 怖がらずにおいで
Come to this pleasant paradise without fear
おいで
Come on
そう、いつも通りの毎日に イロドリと
Yes, giving color to your usual everyday life
アソビゴコロ 召し上がれ ブレンド・エス
And playfulness, enjoy, Blend S
Welcome to...
わたし達と一緒に
Together with us
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
An dazzling wonder day-dream
愛情マシマシ 煩脳ナデナデ
Petting your worldly desires with extra affection
誠心誠意 つとめます いえす！
We will serve you with utmost sincerity, yes!
キミの元気チャージに
To recharge your energy
ひと役買えるかな
I wonder if we can do our part
こーいった感じも
This kind of style
あーいった感じも
And that kind of style too
意外と悪くないでしょ？
Isn't it surprisingly not bad?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, buono, I want to blend
キミにきゅんきゅんきゅん ハートにぱんぱんぱん
Heart-throbbing for you, pounding in your heart
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, buono, I want to blend.
お口にあいますか？
Is it to your liking?
お好み聞かせてね
Tell me what you prefer!
お口にあうといいな
I hope it suits your taste!
というわけで、引き続きゲストブロックをお送りしました！
And with that, we've presented the guest block!
どうだったかな？どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
はい、ということで、このあとはですね、
重大発表もございますので、ぜひ最後まで見てね！
Yes, and after this, we have some major announcements,
so please watch until the end!
はい、そんなゲストブロックの後半なんですが、
ころさんと「かわいこチェック」でしっぽフリフリしました。
Yes, in the second half of the guest block,
Korone-san and I wagged our tails to "Kawaiko Check"!
そして、みこちと「ベイビーダンス」をお送りしましたね。
一緒になんか私服衣装でね、シナジーあったんじゃないかなって思いました。
And then, Mikochi and I performed "Baby Dance."
Since we both wore casual outfits, I think we had great synergy!
そして、そして、フワモコちゃんと「ぼなぺてぃーと♡S」をお届けしました！
And then, we brought you "Bon Appétit S" with Fuwamoko-chan!
いや、もうフワモコちゃんとね、一緒にね、
こうやって3Dでライブしたいなと思ってたので、
I've always wanted to do a 3D live
together with Fuwamoko-chan like this,
もう念願、念願かなって、AZKiのね、やりたいことを全部、
全部、詰め込んだゲストパートでございました！
so it was a dream come true! This guest part packed in
absolutely everything AZKi wanted to do!
はい、ということで、重大発表もあるんですけど、
その前に皆さん、あのお知らせがございます！
All right, although there are major announcements,
before that, everyone, I have some news!
AZKi誕生日記念2025、グッズ販売告知！
こちらをご覧ください！
AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025 merchandise sales announcement!
Please take a look at this!
うおー！今回も、ならならなんと、
盛りだくさんでございます！
Wow! This time we have
an absolute ton of items again!
今回イラストはD福先生に描いていただきました！
ありがとうございます！
The illustration for this year was drawn by D-Fuku-sensei!
Thank you so much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちら！
Let's check out the details. First up is this!
だだだ、抱き枕カバー！
A body pillow cover!
ということで、今回のゆるふわな私服の衣装で寝転がっている
AZKiの、抱き枕カバーが出ます！うわー！
Yes, a body pillow cover featuring AZKi lying down
in this cozy, casual outfit is coming out! Wow!
まさかグッズになるとは思いもよりませんでしたが、
ぜひチェックしてください！
I never expected this to become merchandise,
but please be sure to check it out!
えー、続いては、こちら！缶バッジセット！
Next up is this! The pin badge set!
えー、こちらね、ハートの形をした缶バッジとなっております。
These are heart-shaped pin badges.
キラキラのホログラム仕様となっておりますので、
いっぱい、いっぱいね、つけてほしいなと思います。
They have a shiny hologram finish,
so I hope you put them on lots of things!
続いては、こちら！開拓者ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Next up is this! The Pioneer plush keychain!
えー、ということで、ホロライブフレンズ with u のAZKiと、
だいたいあの同じぐらいのね、ちっちゃいサイズになってますので、
Yes, it's a small size, almost the same as the
"hololive friends with u" AZKi plush,
一緒に、あの持ち歩いてもらえるようなサイズ感となっておりますので、
making it the perfect size to carry around with you,
一緒にね、あずぬいと、開拓者ぬいで、お出かけしてほしいなと思います！
so I hope you go out with both Azu-plush and Pioneer-plush!
続いては、こちら！開拓者アイマスク！
Next up is this! The Pioneer sleep mask!
まあ今回、抱き枕カバーと一緒に、もうね、安眠できるね、
グッズをね、ご用意いたしましたので、
Along with the body pillow cover, we've prepared
sleep-friendly goods for you,
こちらもぜひ、えー、寝るときに使ってほしいなと思います。
so I hope you use this when you go to sleep too!
えー、そして続いては、こちら！ASMRボイス！
And next is this! The ASMR voice pack!
ボイスタイトルは「AZKiのわがままをきいて」というね、
The title of the voice pack is "Listen to AZKi's Selfishness."
ちょっとAZKiがちょっとしたわがままを言って、
君をね、デートに誘うシチュエーションとなっておりますので、
It's a scenario where AZKi acts a bit selfish
and asks you out on a date!
今回のね、このゆるふわ私服衣装のAZKiを思い浮かべて聞いてください！
Please listen to it while imagining AZKi
in this cozy, casual outfit!
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます！こちら！
We also have full-set purchase bonuses! Here they are!
なんと数量限定は、AZKiの直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、
特典ASMRボイス、タイトルは「寝起きのAZKiと」ということで、
The limited-quantity version includes a postcard-sized photo card
with AZKi's handwritten signature, and a special ASMR voice pack
titled "With AZKi on Waking Up."
こちらね、抱き枕カバーのね、なんかちょっと裏面のイラストをイメージした
シチュエーションとなっておりますので、こちらも一緒に楽しんでいただけたらなと思います！
This scenario is inspired by the back illustration of
the body pillow cover, so I hope you enjoy it!
そして、数量限定が、なくなり次第、えー、箔押しの複製サイン入り
チェキ風ブロマイドカードと、特典ASMRボイス、
Once the limited-quantity version is sold out, we will offer the
standard full set featuring a foil-stamped duplicated signature card
同様の「寝起きのAZKiと」となっておりますので、よろしくお願いします。
and the same ASMR voice pack, so please keep that in mind!
改めて、フルセットはこちらとなります！じゃん！
Once again, here is the full set! Ta-da!
いや、いっぱいね、ありますね！買うならね、やっぱね、フルセットが、いいですよ！
みんな、よろしくね、このあと！
Wow, there are so many items! If you're buying, the full set
is definitely the way to go! Everyone, please check it out later!
はい、そして、さらに！なんとプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典といたしまして、
And furthermore! As a special bonus for
purchasing the premium full set,
去年から発売された、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで
使用できるカードが1枚つきます！
you will receive one card that can be used in the
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME, which was released last year!
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで
購入された方のみ対象となります。
This card is exclusive to those who purchase from
the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP.
特典につくのは、推しをアピールできる、
キーカード、「推しホロメンカード」でございます。
The bonus card is an "Oshi Holomem Card,"
a key card that lets you showcase your favorite member!
カードの詳細や、遊び方については、ホームページをご確認ください。
Please check the official website for details
on the card and how to play.
同梱するカードは、日本語版のみとなります。
Note that the included card will be in Japanese only.
ますので ご了承ください。
...so please be aware of this.
以上、AZKi誕生日記念2025のグッズ情報でした！
That's all for the AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025 merch!
みんな買ってね、ぜひ！
Please make sure to get them!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much!
と、いうことでお待たせいたしました。
And with that, thank you for waiting.
さらに、重大発表ございます。
We have another major announcement.
それでは、お待たせいたしました。
Well then, thank you for waiting...
こちらをご覧ください！
Please take a look at this!
重大発表
Major Announcement
2025.11.05
November 5, 2025
Re://Birth
Re://Start
AZKi New EP
2025.11.05 ON SALE
7/1 21:00より予約受付開始
Pre-orders start on 7/1 at 21:00
はい！ということで、AZKiの新しいEP
Yes! And so, AZKi's new EPs...
『Re://Start』と『Re://Birth』が11月5日にリリースすることが決定しましたー！
...'Re://Start' and 'Re://Birth' are set to be released on November 5th!
今回は初めてとなる2作同時リリースとなっております。
This will be our very first dual-release!
このあと21時より、hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPと、
Pre-orders will open at 21:00 today on the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP...
全国のCDショップで予約が開始されます！
...and CD shops nationwide!
精度1枚目の『Re://Start』には、
The first EP, 'Re://Start', will feature...
AZKiの新しい魅力が詰まった新曲4曲。
...4 brand new songs highlighting my new charms.
2枚目の『Re://Birth』には、
The second EP, 'Re://Birth', will feature...
イノナカミュージック時代の楽曲4曲のリアレンジバージョンが収録されます。
...rearranged versions of 4 songs from my INNK Music era.
そして、CD限定特典として、それぞれボーナストラックに
Additionally, as CD-exclusive bonuses, each EP...
すいちゃんと歌った『The Last Frontier』が1種類ずつ収録されます。
...will feature a different version of 'The Last Frontier' sung with Sui-chan!
また、通常盤には限定特典として
Also, standard editions will come with...
ランダムアナザージャケットが1枚ついてきます。
...one random alternative jacket as a limited bonus.
なんとこちらには数量限定で私の、
And some of these might even be...
直筆サイン入りが入っているかも？とのことです。
...hand-signed by me in limited quantities!
各種CDショップでの購入特典はこちらです！
Here are the purchase bonuses at various CD shops!
特典の絵柄は後日発表します。
The actual designs will be revealed at a later date.
さらに、ホロライブオフィシャルショップでは
Furthermore, on the hololive OFFICIAL SHOP,
セットになったコンプリート盤を発売します！
we'll be selling a Complete Edition bundle!
コンプリート盤にはここでしか手に入らない
The Complete Edition comes with...
たくさんの特典もついております。
...many exclusive bonuses that can only be obtained here!
数に限りがございますのでお早めに！
Supplies are limited, so please hurry!
そして、1点！
Also, one quick note!
ホロライブオフィシャルショップのアルバム購入について注意事項がございます。
There are precautions for purchasing albums on the hololive OFFICIAL SHOP.
完全生産限定コンプリート盤は発売日でのお届けとなりますので、
The Limited Complete Edition is scheduled to deliver on the release day,
EP以外のグッズとの商品は同時購入できません！
so it cannot be purchased together with other non-EP merchandise!
通常盤は他のグッズとの同時購入が可能ですが、
Standard editions can be purchased with other merch,
店頭販売日以降のお届けになる可能性があるので、ご注意ください。
but they may arrive after the retail release date, so please keep this in mind.
詳しくは販売サイトの注意事項をご確認ください。
For details, please check the precautions on the sales website.
はい！そして最後に、もう一つお知らせあります。
Yes! And finally, I have one more announcement.
今回ね、発表したこのニューEP『Re://Start』の中から、
Tonight at 24:00, we will digitally release...
『未来カンパネラ』という楽曲を本日24時にデジタルリリースします！
...'Mirai Campanella,' a track from the new EP 'Re://Start'!
わー！新曲だー！
Wow! A brand new song!
配信終了後にはミュージックビデオも
After the stream ends, the music video...
プレミア公開しちゃいますということで、ぜひチェックしてください！
...will also premiere, so please be sure to check it out!
わー！いっぱい情報がありましたが、みんなついてこれましたか？はい！
Whew! There was so much info, but did you all manage to keep up? Great!
ということで、ライブも次の曲で最後になります。
With that, the next song will be the final song of today's live.
最後はね、AZKiの新しい曲を聴いていただきたいと思います！
To close things out, I'd like to perform my new song for all of you!
それでは、聴いてください。未来カンパネラ。
Without further ado, please listen to: "Mirai Campanella".
もっと
More...
鏡よ 教えて
Mirror, mirror, tell me...
私の証は
Where can I find...
どこにあるのだろう
...the proof of who I am?
分からない 分からないよ
I don't know, I just don't know...
周りと比べたってさ
Even if I compare myself to others,
虚しくなるだけ
it only leaves me feeling empty.
あぁ ノイズが 海鳴りのように ナミダを奪う
Ah, the noise steals away my tears like the roaring of the sea.
切り取った風景を
Let's turn these captured scenery...
道しるべにしよう
...into our guiding light.
そうだ 傷ついた感情も
Yes, even the hurt feelings...
連れて行くから
I'll take you with me,
そっと響くカンパネラ 新しい未来を感じてる
The softly echoing campanella, I feel a new future
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ？
Even if I'm scared, I have no choice but to move forward, right?
遠くまで
To the far distance
届けこの祈りよ 光となれ
Let this prayer reach, and become the light
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい「私」という答えを
More, more, even if only little by little, the answer called "me"
もっと もっと…
More, more...
夜空よ教えて
Tell me, night sky,
私の証は
will my proof of existence
輝けるのかな 見つけたい 見つけたいよ
be able to shine? I want to find it, I want to find it
誰かの決めたレールは苦しくなるだけ
The rails laid out by someone else only make me feel choked
ねえノイズも力に変えるよ
Hey, I'll turn even the noise into strength
ココロに誓う
I swear to my heart
錆びついた運命の歯車を回そう ほら
Let's turn the rusted gears of fate, look
着飾った感情は脱ぎ捨てるから
Because I will cast off dressed-up emotions
そっと紡ぐシンフォニア 叶えたい願いを信じてる
The softly spun symphonia, I believe in the wish I want to grant
胸を張って歌うしかないでしょ？
With my head held high, I have no choice but to sing, right?
全力で
With all my might
やがて希望の歌に変わる日まで
Until the day it eventually changes into a song of hope
悩みながらでいい すべてが宝物
More, more, even if I'm worrying, everything is a treasure
いつの日かこの声を受け取ってくれたなら
If someday you receive this voice of mine
この言葉を君に「もう大丈夫、一人じゃない」
I'll send these words to you: "It's alright, you are not alone"
強い想いをつなぐよ
I will connect our strong feelings
一歩踏み出してみた 優しく世界は微笑む
I took a step forward, and the world smiled gently
高鳴る気持ちに身を任せて さあ行こう
Entrusting myself to my pounding heart, now, let's go
そっと響くカンパネラ 新しい未来を感じてる
The softly echoing campanella, I feel a new future
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ？
Even if I'm scared, I have no choice but to move forward, right?
遠くまで
To the far distance
届けこの祈りよ 光となれ
Let this prayer reach, and become the light
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい「私」という答えを
More, more, even if only little by little, the answer called "me"
もっと もっと…
More, more...
ごめん、待った？
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
ごめんね、ライブ終わった後マネージャーさんに呼ばれちゃって。
Sorry, after the concert ended, my manager called for me.
もちろん打ち上げもあったけど、君と会うためにキャンセルしたんだからね。
Of course there was an after-party, but I canceled it to meet you, okay?
改めて、今日はライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Once again, thank you for coming to my concert today!
アリーナ席の右の方にいたよね？
You were on the right side of the arena seats, right?
ちゃんと見つけたよ。
I spotted you clearly.
実は今日、花火大会なんだって。
Actually, I heard there's a fireworks festival today.
こんな都会で花火あがるの、ロマンチックだなぁ。
Fireworks going off in a city like this is so romantic.
ねえ、見て見て！
Hey, look, look!
今日のライブのキービジュアルだよ。
That's the key visual from today's concert.
もしかしたら、ここでも流れてたのかな？
Maybe it was being shown here too?
ついさっきのことだから、ちょっと恥ずかしいよ。
Since it happened just a moment ago, it's a bit embarrassing.
でも、とっても楽しかったな。
But it was so much fun.
あ、雨？
Ah, rain?
どうしよう、私、傘持ってないよ。
What should I do? I don't have an umbrella.
あ、傘、持ってきてくれたんだ。
Oh, you brought an umbrella for me.
ありがとう、かっこいいじゃん。
Thank you, that's pretty cool of you.
でも、傘一つしかないってことは、これって、相合い傘だよね？
But since there's only one umbrella, does this mean... we're sharing an umbrella?
私、相合い傘って初めてで。これってさ…
Sharing an umbrella is a first for me. This is...
わあ、ドキドキするね
Wow, I'm so excited.
あ、雨が止んだ！
Oh, the rain stopped!
通り雨だったのかな？
Was it just a passing shower?
なんか雨止んで嬉しいような、悲しいような…
Somehow, I feel happy but also a bit sad...
もっと君と相合い傘したかったな
I wanted to share an umbrella with you longer.
なんてね！
Just kidding!
雨も止んだし
The rain has stopped,
雨で人通りも少なくなったしさ
and there aren't many people around, so...
グリコゲームでもしようよ
Let's play the Glico game!
ここからスタートね！
We start from here, okay!
行くよ！
Here I go!
じゃんけん、ぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors!
やったー！私の勝ち！
Yay! I won!
ち・よ・こ・れ・い・と！
C-H-O-C-O-L-A-T-E!
ちょっと何にやにやして見てるの？
Why are you grinning like that?
え？可愛いって？
What? You think I'm cute?
もう、ちょっと恥ずかしいからやめてよー
Gosh, stop it, that's embarrassing!
次行くよ！
Next round!
じゃんけん、ぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors!
ぐ・り・こ！
G-L-I-C-O!
だからちょっとにやにやにやめてってばー
I told you, stop grinning like that!
次行くよ！
Next round!
じゃんけん、ぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors!
ぱ・い・な・つ・ぷ・る！
P-I-N-E-A-P-P-L-E!
もう、じゃんけん弱すぎだよ！
Wow, you're so bad at this!
絶対わざと負けてるでしょ？
You're definitely losing on purpose!
もう、いい加減にしてよね
Play seriously, okay?
え？なに？
Huh? What?
こっち来てって？
"Come over here"?
どこ行くの？
Where are we going?
なに、なに？見せたいものがある？
What is it? You have something to show me?
あのモニターを見ろって？
Look at that monitor?
3、2、1？
3, 2, 1?
え？え？どういうこと？
What? What's going on?
お誕生日おめでとう？
"Happy Birthday"?
えー！ありがとう！
No way! Thank you!
サプライズしてくれたんだ！
You planned a surprise for me!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
いつも一番近くで応援してくれて本当にありがとう
Thank you so much for always supporting me by my side.
これからもよろしくね
Please continue to support me.
きれい…
It's beautiful...
素敵な誕生日にしてくれて、ありがとう
Thank you for giving me such a wonderful birthday.
お礼にこの後、君だけのアンコールライブするね
To thank you, I'll perform an encore live just for you after this.
これからもずっと一緒にいてね
Please stay with me forever.
AZKi 7th Birthday Live Sweet Pop Story
新衣装お披露目 / 重大発表あり
New Outfit Reveal & Major Announcement